how long you've been doing stand up now
James man like about 10 years 10 years
how old are you I am early
30s what are you
pregnant I'm early 30s it's not what you
think don't judge me cuz listen if
they're doing some high school movie and
they need the dumb dude who still can't
graduate I want to be that dude yeah so
you never want to let the age n no uh
where you from I'm from Los Angeles
South Central adjacent wow yeah wow yeah
cuz if I say South Central you're going
to think of a your favorite scene from
like boys in the hood or baby boy and I
grew up where they kept the craft
Services you know what I'm saying like
like two blocks away from the scene was
where I was growing up I got it but you
can see it you can see see it you can
see where this was happening at exactly
he like don't go down there it's crazy
down there it was too blurry to know who
was the good dude and the bad dude you
know got you okay I like that I just
learned something new today adjacent um
do you feel like there's a difference in
your style of n because you're a West
Coast based stand comedian definitely
because I mean I feel like I'm an LA
dude from you know I care about how I
look there's a certain way we talk we
enunciate you know I don't know what is
that what is that supposed to mean you
know
La you know La guys we talk this way
okay you know properly improper okay or
something but you know I don't have like
a sther draw I know I'm I don't know if
I'm going to agree with that I don't
have that I don't have I'm not like East
Coast B sun I don't have a draw I'm just
like that l
hire him immediately you know I mean I
want to show youall some pictures of
James from back in the day all right
when James first started doing comedy
okay uh let's look at the Hat this is
what I mean uh that's that's chocolate
Sunday's First Impressions First
Impressions that's where you get three
minutes and then they're like no more
and I took it straight to the face okay
like three minutes let's just let's just
back up and let's just not you didn't I
mean pause I mean I failed miserably
there you go there you go with my jokes
they did not
land you didn't take anything to the no
I didn't took I
didn't I took silence and disappointment
to the face there you go all right now
we're clear I'm about to send you off to
enter the next level man this is big one
of the biggest moments in your life
right now oh yeah and I want you to
treat it as such yes sir I don't want
you hitting the stage with those pants
on oh no this ain't even the stage
outfit oh this isn't the stage outfit I
got a whole different arsenal of apparel
that's going to be just d bued with the
material I feel much better now watch me
do watch me okay well go on
man